Guide to the Irving Godt Papers 1952-2002 (Bulk 1970-1992) MC 206
New York University Archives
- Series III: Research Materials
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Various photocopied works (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1 List books, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Summer Institute in the Theory and Practice of Sixteenth-Century Music, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - A Program of Concert Programs, various (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Various photocopied works (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Fucci 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence--Cherubini Index, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence--Italy, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence--Newsweek, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence--William Elders, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence--Reese, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence--NEH Grant, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence--Music Review, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence--Mendel, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence--Grove, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence--University of Minnesota, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence--Dittmer, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence--New Grove Dictionary of Music, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence--Joseph Shipley, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence--Brunner, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Series V: Publications/Speeches
  - "Style Periods of Music History Considered Analytically"/American Musicological Society, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "Marsilio Ficino on the Sublime Effect of Song", undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "A Major Angel Concert in Ferrara", undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "An Essay on Word Painting"/College Music Symposium, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - "Madrigalism: A Polemical View", undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "Two Brief Reports: The Fucci Grilanda Cautionary Accidentals", 1977 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "The Latest Renaissance Instrument: The Voice"/Divisions, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - "A Monteverdi Source Reappears"/Music & Letters, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - "C.P.E. Bach: His Mark"/College Music Symposium, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Editorial/Journal of the American Musicological Society, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Letter to the Editor/Scientific American, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "Music, the Servant of Poetry?"/College Music Symposium, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Motivic Integrations in Josquin's Motets"/Journal of Music Theory, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - "A Lesson in Musica ficta from Guillaume Costeley"/The Music Review, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "The Restoration of Josquin's Ave mundi spes, Maria"/Tjidschrift van de Vereniging Voor Nederlandse Muziekgeschiedenis, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - "Choral Conductors Forum: The Motets in the Josquin Edition"/American Choral Review, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - "Mozart's Real Joke", undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "Unifying Melodic Features in a Variety of Styles"/American Musicological Society, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - "John Bennet and the Directional Convention", undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - "Unifying Motivic Features"/American Musicological Society, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - "Reading Ligatures from Their Ground State"/Early Music, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Gasparini, Marcello, and New York"/Bulletin of Research in the Humanities, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - "Renaissance Paraphrase Technique: A Descriptive Tool"/Music Theory Spectrum, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - "Costeley"/New Grove Dictionary, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - "Concerning the Down-Sharp", undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - "A Monteverdi Source Reappears: The Grilanda of F.M. Fucci", undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Fucci--Recovery, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - "New Voices and Old Theory: A Synthesis?", undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - "Purcell and Dido (Also Aeneas)"/American Musicological Society, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - "The Most Momentous Development"/The Music Academy of Ljubljana, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - "Three Painted Ladies in Bologna and One in Vienna", undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - "Marianna Martines"/American Musicological Society, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - "Prince Henry as Absalom"/Music & Letters, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - "Madrigalism in Spain Before, During, and After the Voyage of Columbus"/24th International Congress on Medieval Studies, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Piece published in 1984--inquiry, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - English Clash, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - "The Restoration of Josquin's Ave Mundi Spes, Maria, and Some Observations on Restoration", undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Musik"/translation, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Monteverdi's Arianna: A Study of Various Aspects of the Fragment: Part I", undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "How to Destroy a University", undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Costeley, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Untitled speech/American Musicological Society, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Manure and Roses: Thoughts on Choral Arrangement (Revised)", undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Josquin: Ave mundi (correction), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Josquin: Ave mundi 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Josquin: Ave mundi: Reading version, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "A New Look at the Missa Papae Marcello"/American Musicological Society, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "C.P.E. Bach: His Mark"--corrections, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "New Voices and Old Theory: A Synthesis?", undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Word Painting", undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Hi-Fi Publication--Draft, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous program notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Leighton--Chapter Four, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "A Major Angel Concert in Ferrara", undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Ercole's Angel Concert", undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Schonsleder's De Textu: An Early Case Book on Word Painting", undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Musica Ficta"--Corrections, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Chevalier/Monteverdi, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Motivic Integrations in Josquin's Motets", undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "A Monteverdi Source Reappears", undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "The Latest Early Instrument: The Voice", undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Unpublications, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Materials regarding Irgo's Encyclopedia of Music, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "The Vatican Organum Treatise", undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Various writings, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Various writings, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - "Beneventan Chant", 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "Madrigalism: A Polemical View", 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publication drafts, various (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "Schonsleder De Textu: An Early Case-Book on Word Painting", undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - "Manure and Roses: Thoughts on Choral Arrangement", undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - "Mozart's Real Joke" (revised), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "Mozart's Real Joke", undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - "Prince Henry as Absalom in David's Lamentations", undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Josquin--Ave mundi, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "101 Assertions About Underlay", undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "The Meistersinger: A Hidden Heritage", undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "On the Break-up of the Traditional Tonal System"/American Musicological Society, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "The Cello"/HiFi Stereo Review, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Down-Sharp Dubitations", undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "A Thesaurus of Examples in Reserve", undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "John Bennet and the Directional Convention"/Center for Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "Renaissance Paraphrase Technique: A Descriptive Tool", undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - "The Fortunes of Arianna"/American Musicological Society, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Tools for the Formal Study of Word Painting"/American Musicological Society, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "Education? A Sermon to My Colleagues", 2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Book Review: "Tonality and Atonality in Sixteenth Century Music" by Edward E. Lowinsky, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous poetry, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - "A Whip to Lash Loose", undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Gaudent Brevitate Moderni", undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - "The Mikado: A Lecture"/Kent State University, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Loose Manuscripts and Scores: 1 of 3, various (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Loose Manuscripts and Scores: 2 of 3, various (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Loose Manuscripts and Scores: 3 of 3, various (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous poetry, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous poetry, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Travel diary, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - "The Bubble", undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Collegium Musicum: First Annual List, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Festival of Baroque Musicke, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Resume: 1 of 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Resume: 2 of 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - The Cosmos and Other Minor Matters, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Eye of the Beholder, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous writings, various (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous published articles, various (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous writings, various (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Perfidia: A Possible Addition to Baroque Musical Terminology", undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Beethoven, various (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Impressionism, various (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous writings, various (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Motivic Integration in Josquin's Motets", undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous writings, various (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous published articles, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Cue sheet for style analysis: Basic components for analytic hypotheses, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "A Descriptive Tool for Paraphrase", undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Three Painted Ladies in Bologna and One in Vienna", 1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - "A Motivic Secret of the Eroica", undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "Toward a More Formal Definition of Music", undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Schubert, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Publications, various (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "Vienna and Schubert", undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Poetry, various (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "The Tuition Remission Plan", undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Some People (Private Views)", undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - 1570 Costeley quints, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 1570 Costeley sugg., undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 1570 Costeley, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - 1570 Costeley contra, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "A Major Angel Concert in Ferrara"/American Musicological Society, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mozart: Divertim, Palestrina, Missa Papae Marcello, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Arianna, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dictionary entries, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dictionary entries, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dictionary entries, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "Style Periods of Music History Considered Analytically", undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "The Mass of Barcelona: How Many Hands? How Much Mass?"/American Musicological Society, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous materials, including unpublished poetry
  - "The Sentiments Expressed…(Some Selected People)", undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - "It'll Be a Blast: A Bunch of Poems of the Bomb", undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Two Pounds of Poems, Cheap", undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Some Songs of Morning and Evening", undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Cogito Irgo Sum", 1952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Poems: Two Pounds, Cheap", undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Cherce Verse or (Something for Everybody)", undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Binder of photocopied scores, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Liturgical Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Listening Test List, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Listening Test List, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - LT--Instructor, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Seven Liberal Arts, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Landmarks of Early Opera, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - KYR IX, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Key & Mode, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Crusades, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cone: One Hundred Metronomes, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chant bibl., undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Black Notation, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Baroque Psycho-Bio, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Baroque Ornaments, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - American, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Organum--Motet, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Organal Performance, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Outline 301, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Outline 302, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Palestrina--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Paraphrase Technique, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Pange lingua, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Phonemics 1 & 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Piano Genealogies, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Pop vs. Art, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Psalm Numbers, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - When do you quote? What is FDQ?, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Renaissance vs. Baroque ig., undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Renaissance vs. Baroque ig., undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Responsorial Chant, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Rhythmic Modes, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Rules for Writers, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - SHMRG --20, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Reasons, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Berg, works, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Gilles de Binchois--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Bizet: Carmen, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Brahms--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Bruckner--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Bruckner/Cuyler Symphony, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Berlioz--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Josquin Desprez--Ave Maria Motivic Unity, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Dufay--Missa Sancti Jacobi, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Guillaume Dufay--Et in terra, ad modum Tube, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Guillaume Dufay--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Dunstable--Veni, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Dunstable--Veni (Analysis), undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Antonin Dvorak--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dvorak Symphony No. 8, op. 88, undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Franck--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Franck--Symphony in D, undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Gabrieli--Canzona "La spiritata", undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Gabrieli--O Jesu mi ducis., undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Gabrieli--O Jesu mi ducis., undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Gherardello--Tosto che l'alba, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Gluck, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Beach--Music's Ten Commandments, undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Beethoven Sym. No. 3 Analysis, undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Beethoven--Heiligenstadt Testament, undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Beethoven--Piano Sonata #32 op. 111, mvt. 1: Analysis, undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Beethoven--Quartet op. 95, undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Beethoven--Pf Sonata #32, undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Ars Nova Notation, undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Back Tree, undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - C.P.E. Bach--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Bach--Jesu, der du Meine Steele (3 recitativo), undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Bach--Suite in B minor, undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Bela Bartok--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Byrd, William--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Chopin--Berceuse (A-20), undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Chopin--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Chopin--Style and Contribution, undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Clausae Tenors, undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Corelli--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Corelli--Sonata, undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Couperin--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Couperin Tree, undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - The Couperins, undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Debussy--Trois Nocturnes (II: Nuages), undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Debussy--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Desprez--Miss de Beata Virgine, undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Gaude--Amus Omnes in Domino, undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Kyrie IX (analysis), undated (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Anon. Kyrie/All (Kyrie IX: Alle Pascha nostrum), undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Anon. Sumer canon (Sumer is icumen in), undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Gloria--troped (anon.), undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Venit ad Petrum, undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Veni Creator Spiritus text, undated (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Veni Creator Spiritus tune, undated (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Adam de la Hodle: Bonne Amourette, undated (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Arcadelt: Il bianco e dolce, undated (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - A 23 (6), undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Verdi--Rigoletto, undated (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Verdi--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Antonio Vivaldi--Concerto Grosso, op. 3, no. 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Vivaldi--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Wagner--Die Meistersinger von Nurnberg, undated (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Wagner--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - "Old" music (Warlock), undated (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - What do they know? (Warlock), undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - C.M. von Weber--Der Freischutz (syn), undated (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Weber--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Cue sheet for SHMRG, undated (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - SHMRG ROM #2, undated (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - SHMRG ROM #3, undated (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Ren vs. Bar, undated (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - Med vs. Ren, undated (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Style Periods (not drawn to scale), undated (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Table of contents (1), undated (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Tables of Content--Misc., undated (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Text Diagram, undated (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Thomas Kontors, undated (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Trombone in M.A. & Ren., undated (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Translations continued (2), undated (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - Translations Mu 301 p. 7-11, undated (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - Word Painting I & II, undated (Box 21, Folder 117)
  - Tchaikovsky--Works, undated (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - Vaqueiras--Kalenda Maya--Analysis, undated (Box 21, Folder 119)
  - Kalenda Maya--Vaqueiras, undated (Box 21, Folder 120)
  - Variation Tech, undated (Box 21, Folder 121)
  - Verdi, undated (Box 21, Folder 122)
  - Musica Enchiriadis, undated (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Node Elements, undated (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Modes (8), undated (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - MH 302 rough outline, undated (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Mass Plan, undated (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Madrigal History, undated (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Lutheran Cantata Types, undated (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Liturgical Day, undated (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - "To Itch His Own", 1953 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Composer Index Work Copy, undated (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - PAL Masses, undated (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Entries from Vannes, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Musica Polyglossa (w/correspondence), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Musica Polyglossa, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Benedetto Marcello--Magnificat in F, Transcription, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Costelay Folder 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Costelay Folder 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Costelay Folder 3, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Costelay Folder 4, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Costelay Folder 5, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Collegium Musicum Pronunciation Guide, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ph.D. Guidelines (AMS), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Canon, Jacob Meiland, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - C.P.E. Bach, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Various photocopied scores, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Yale (various photocopied scores), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Handwritten notes and scores, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Magnum Opus Musicum (MOM), undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Binder of handwritten scores, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "Guillaume Costeley: Life and Works, Volume II", undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Two Pounds of Poems, Cheap", undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 1570 Costeley Tenor, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Small book with handwritten scores, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Binder of photocopies and handwritten notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous teaching materials, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - MUS 306 photocopies, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - MUS 302 supplementary materials, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bonnet Chassant: Puy de musique Evreux, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Binder of miscellaneous handwritten scores and notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Series VII: Marianna Martines research material
  General note
  Although the authority name from the Library of Congress for this composer is Marianne Martinez, Irving Godt refers to her as Marianna Martines throughout most of this collection.
  Scope and Contents note
  The materials dating from the 18th and 19th century are reproductions (done at an unknown date) of original works dated from the 18th and 19th century, not the original works themselves.
  - Subseries A: Musical Scores
    - Cellokonzert Number 3, G-Dur, Composed by Joachim Raff, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Concerti in C Transcription and Solo Parts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Concerto in A, Parts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Concerto in A, Transcript and Solo Part, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Concerto in C Parts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Concerto in G Score, 1772 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Dixit Dominus, A-R Laser Masters, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Dixit Dominus, Berlin, circa 1774 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Dixit Dominus, Edits of, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Dixit Dominus, parts, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Dixit Dominus, parts, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Dixit Dominus, parts A-R Editions, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Dixit Dominus, parts, Edits of, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Dixit Dominus Score, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Dixit Dominus Score, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Dixit Dominus Score, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Dixit Dominus Score, A-R Editions, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Dixit Dominus Score and Parts, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Dixit Dominus Score with annotations, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Dixit Dominus, sent to Bologna, part 1, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Dixit Dominus, sent to Bologna, part 2, 1774 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Dixit Dominus, spiral bound with annotations, 1774 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Dixit Dominus, Transcription, 1774 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Dixit Dominus, Vienna, 1774 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Il Consiglio with parts, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Il Primo Amore with parts, 1778 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - In Exitu Florence Part 1 of 2, Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)